[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Animal foods generally contain more saturated fats that plant foods.", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is is average growth rate of normal hair follicles on the human scalp?", "correct_answer": "400 \u00b5m per day", "incorrect_answers": ["1 mm per day", "100 \u00b5m per day", "800 \u00b5m per day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This perennial bulbous plant from the family of Liliaceae is the national flower of Iran.", "correct_answer": "Tulip", "incorrect_answers": ["Lily", "Rose", "Sagebrush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This bridge, that spans the Tagus River, is the longest bridge in Europe.", "correct_answer": "Vasco da Gama Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["Vizcaya Bridge", "Guadiana International Bridge", "Merida Bridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On May 6, 1937 the Hindenburg exploded as it tried to dock in the Lakehurst Naval Station in New Jersey. Out of the 97 people on the Zeppelin, how many died?", "correct_answer": "35", "incorrect_answers": ["90", "96", "97"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nightmare does Shrek have about his babies when he learns that he is going to be a father in the movie Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "A countless number of babies terrorizes him.", "incorrect_answers": ["Fiona gives birth to Pinocchio.", "The babies look like Prince Charming.", "Fiona and the babies chase him with torches."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before he began his acting career, this Rushmore and Spun star was a drummer and songwriter for the band Phantom Plane.", "correct_answer": "Jason Schwartzman", "incorrect_answers": ["Bill Murray", "Nicolas Cage", "Seth Rogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first fly by\u201d for the planet Mars occurred in this year.", "correct_answer": "1965", "incorrect_answers": ["1975", "1955", "1945"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Algonquin wedding feasts include many traditional American Indian foods, as well as this type of meat.", "correct_answer": "Deer", "incorrect_answers": ["Pork", "Hare", "Horse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the quantity of caffeine in an average chocolate?", "correct_answer": "as much as in a cup of decaffeinated coffee", "incorrect_answers": ["as much as in a cup of tea", "as much as in a cup of coffee", "as much as in a glass of coke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American actor portrayed Private First Class James Francis Ryan in Steven Spielbergs 1998 movie masterpiece Saving Private Ryan?", "correct_answer": "Matt Damon", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Affleck", "Tom Hanks", "Jeremy Davies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the movie The Graduate released?", "correct_answer": "1967", "incorrect_answers": ["1970", "1969", "1971"]}]